{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Italian4.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "voi avete fretta"
            ],
            "answer": "Voi avete fretta.",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1516903746.7361836,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all are in a hurry.\"?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho bisogno di un caffe",
                "Io ho bisogno di un caffe"
            ],
            "answer": "Io ho bisogno di un caffe'",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1516903698.316576,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I do need a coffee!\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "loro hanno nove zie e dieci nipoti"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro hanno nove zie e dieci nipoti.",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1516903799.587975,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They have nine aunts and ten nieces.\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tu hai sete",
                "Tu hai sete"
            ],
            "answer": "Tu hai sete.",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516903726.9673762,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You (informal) are thirsty.\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "voi avete",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516903789.366635,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"y'all have\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "abbiamo quattro nonni e sette nipoti"
            ],
            "answer": "Noi abbiamo quattro nonni e sette nipoti.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516903714.2384408,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We have four grandparents and seven nephews.\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sonno",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516903802.331791,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sleep\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "loro hanno",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516903756.0061576,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"they have\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ragione",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516903831.973283,
            "question": "Given the definition \"reason\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lui e"
            ],
            "answer": "lui e'",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516903822.823279,
            "question": "Given the definition \"he is\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "uno zio",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516903859.252692,
            "question": "Given the definition \"an uncle\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "You are hungry",
                "you are hungry"
            ],
            "answer": "You (formal) are hungry.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516903868.5214517,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei ha fame.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho freddo"
            ],
            "answer": "avere freddo",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516903872.1211205,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be cold\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "loro hanno fretta"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro hanno fretta.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516903817.9010353,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They are in a hurry.\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sete",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1516903874.5520868,
            "question": "Given the definition \"thirst\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lui ha fame",
                "lei ha fame"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei ha fame.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516903855.9325426,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She is hungry.\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ci sono dieci uomini e nove donne",
                "Ci sono dieci uomini e nove donne"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono dieci uomini e nove donne.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516903896.895325,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are ten men and nine women.\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tu hai",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903905.273215,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you have (informal)\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quattro stazioni",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903913.8391588,
            "question": "four stations",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hurry",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903908.2247248,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fretta\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "due giorni",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903900.2580938,
            "question": "two days",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "voi avete fretta"
            ],
            "answer": "Voi avete fretta.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903884.0018322,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all are in a hurry.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere paura",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903877.8830962,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be afraid\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "due madri",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903888.5122643,
            "question": "two mothers",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco nove bambine"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco nove bambine.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903939.7576256,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are nine children. (girls)\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "due sere",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903944.444926,
            "question": "two evenings",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere sonno",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903951.2442844,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be sleepy\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "We have four grandparents and seven nephews"
            ],
            "answer": "We have four grandparents and seven nephews.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516903928.6161447,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi abbiamo quattro nonni e sette nipoti.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "loro hanno sonno"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro hanno sonno.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516904018.737062,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They are sleepy.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Lei ha otto zii e sei cugini"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei ha otto zii e sei cugini.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516904036.0372887,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She has eight uncles and six cousins.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lui ha freddo",
                "Lui ha freddo"
            ],
            "answer": "Lui ha freddo.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904015.1137385,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He is cold.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "there is one student",
                "There is one student"
            ],
            "answer": "There is one student.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516904024.8229218,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' uno studente.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Anche, loro hanno fretta",
                "E anche, loro hanno fretta"
            ],
            "answer": "Anche loro hanno fretta.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904091.598006,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They are in a hurry, too.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am thirsty"
            ],
            "answer": "I am thirsty.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904043.6031115,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io ho sete.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "y'all have",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904106.2328298,
            "question": "Given the definition \"voi avete\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "She has eight uncles and six cousins"
            ],
            "answer": "She has eight uncles and six cousins.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904054.3732696,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei ha otto zii e sei cugini.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "noi abbiamo freddo"
            ],
            "answer": "Noi abbiamo freddo.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904111.0804,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We are cold.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho bisogno di un caffe"
            ],
            "answer": "Ho bisogno di un caffe'",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904101.5930293,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I need a coffee.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I do need a coffee"
            ],
            "answer": "I do need a coffee!",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516904131.2740767,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Io ho bisogno di un caffe'\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "not",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904093.5407584,
            "question": "Given the definition \"non\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho sette",
                "ho sete"
            ],
            "answer": "Io ho sete.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904162.307465,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am thirsty.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "otto bambini",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516904192.4608624,
            "question": "Eight boy children.",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Lei ha fame"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei ha fame.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904182.2700975,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You (formal) are hungry.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere ragione",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904157.3244927,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be right\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tre ragazze"
            ],
            "answer": "tre regazze",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904153.644413,
            "question": "three girls",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "uno",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904170.6589782,
            "question": "(a or the) Lui e' ___ studente.",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere fame",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904135.0253417,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be hungry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho una famiglia piccola",
                "Ho una famiglia piccola",
                "Io ho una famiglia piccola"
            ],
            "answer": "io ho una famiglia piccola.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516904216.5118525,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I have a small family.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516904326.206357,
            "question": "(a or the) Ecco ___ signor Belli.",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Maria is hungry",
                "Mario is hungry"
            ],
            "answer": "Mario is hungry.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904298.2524712,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Mario ha fame.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco tre famiglie"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco tre famiglie.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904306.5160668,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are three families.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "They have 9 aunts and 10 nephews"
            ],
            "answer": "They have nine aunts and ten nieces.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904264.3714035,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro hanno nove zie e dieci nipoti.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "zia",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904218.902901,
            "question": "Given the definition \"aunt\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono tre sorelle e quattro fratelli"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono tre sorelle e quattro fratelli.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904229.7262254,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are three sisters and four brothers.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you have"
            ],
            "answer": "you have (informal)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904292.3014228,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tu hai\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "here are seven families",
                "Here are seven families"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are seven families.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904333.849334,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco sette famiglie.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un giorno",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904411.177841,
            "question": "one day / a day",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904407.9533582,
            "question": "(a or the) Lei e' ___ studentessa.",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lei ha",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904352.1718905,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"she has\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904380.0393322,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to have\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here is 12 people",
                "Here are 12 people",
                "Here are twelve people"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are twelve people.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904403.6583555,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco dodici persone.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cugino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904358.099883,
            "question": "Given the definition \"male cousin\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "abbiamo"
            ],
            "answer": "noi abbiamo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904364.9947956,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"we have\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tre signori"
            ],
            "answer": "tre ginori",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904368.9557478,
            "question": "three gentlemen",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un nipote",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904476.6681187,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a nephew\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tu hai paura",
                "Tu hai paura"
            ],
            "answer": "Tu hai paura.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904464.1886482,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You (informal) are afraid.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "THere are 10 men and 9 women",
                "There are ten men and 9 women"
            ],
            "answer": "There are ten men and nine women.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904425.573439,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono dieci uomini e nove donne.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "and also they are in a hurry",
                "They are in a hurry too"
            ],
            "answer": "They are in a hurry, too.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904453.4402313,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Anche loro hanno fretta.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904490.0639248,
            "question": "(a or the) Ecco ___ signora Belli.",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Lei ha",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904482.0523741,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you have (formal)\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono due studenti"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono due studenti.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904488.271441,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are two students.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lui ha sonno"
            ],
            "answer": "Lui ha sonno.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516904500.5676343,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He is sleepy.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "loro sono"
            ],
            "answer": "loro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904520.0835502,
            "question": "Given the definition \"they\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "one student / a student",
                "a student"
            ],
            "answer": "a (male) student",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904537.0174127,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"uno studente\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are 5 boys and six girls"
            ],
            "answer": "There are five boys and six girls.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904546.0701284,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono cinque ragazzi e sei ragazze.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be in a hurry",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904505.2065632,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere fretta\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cold",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904539.490325,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"freddo\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Lei",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904552.0177717,
            "question": "Given the definition \"you (formal)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "voi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904548.6054084,
            "question": "Given the definition \"y'all\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I do need a coffe",
                "I need a coffee"
            ],
            "answer": "I need a coffee.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904514.7231429,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Ho bisogno di un caffe'\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "they are in a hurry",
                "They are in a hurry"
            ],
            "answer": "They are in a hurry.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904615.3240957,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro hanno fretta.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "they have",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516904651.870093,
            "question": "Given the definition \"loro hanno\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "She is hungry",
                "she is hungry"
            ],
            "answer": "She is hungry.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904558.9690592,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei ha fame.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "we",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904608.7281103,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"noi\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono cinque ragazzi e sei ragazze"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono cinque ragazzi e sei ragazze.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904630.7636158,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are five boys and six girls.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "hot"
            ],
            "answer": "heat",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904571.1372461,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"caldo\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "reason",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904633.7552063,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ragione\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Lei e'"
            ],
            "answer": "lei e'",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904645.438484,
            "question": "Given the definition \"she is\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una sera",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904682.4894893,
            "question": "one evening",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sleepy"
            ],
            "answer": "sleep",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904658.558424,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sonno\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "noi non abbiamo paura"
            ],
            "answer": "Noi non abbiamo paura.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904677.7937822,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We are not afraid.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una nipote",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904686.1370707,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a niece\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you have"
            ],
            "answer": "you have (formal)",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516904697.2222133,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei ha\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco sette famiglie"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco sette famiglie.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904672.2268722,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are seven families.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho"
            ],
            "answer": "io ho",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904690.9462628,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I have\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "an uncle",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904694.7498047,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"uno zio\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be cold",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904727.281418,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere freddo\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "she is",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904703.5418355,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lei e'\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "he",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904698.7018454,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lui\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "afraid"
            ],
            "answer": "fear",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904701.2138042,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"paura\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to be scared"
            ],
            "answer": "to be afraid",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904718.4014933,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere paura\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be thirsty",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904734.0687273,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere sete\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e"
            ],
            "answer": "c'e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904723.1056755,
            "question": "(C'e' | Ci sono) ___ una ragazza.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lui ha",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904729.7850454,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"he has\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am not afraid"
            ],
            "answer": "I am not afraid.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904745.2612822,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io non ho paura.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho fame"
            ],
            "answer": "IO ho fame.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904737.0212283,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am hungry.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "he has",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904754.1888478,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lui ha\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "io",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904758.2326617,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grandmother",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904752.0524657,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nonna\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "aunt",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904756.5166187,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"zia\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere paura",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904741.6766667,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to be afraid\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "due bambini"
            ],
            "answer": "due ragazzi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904748.7809172,
            "question": "two boys",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fame",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904801.2362518,
            "question": "Given the definition \"hunger\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "he is cold"
            ],
            "answer": "He is cold.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904797.4683762,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui ha freddo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "c'e uno studente",
                "C'e uno studente"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' uno studente.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904794.244595,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There is one student.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Mario ha fame"
            ],
            "answer": "Mario ha fame.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904763.60043,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Mario is hungry.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "I",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904799.3874795,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"io\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "non",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904808.0355697,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"not\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to be correct"
            ],
            "answer": "to be right",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904806.2206273,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere ragione\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere caldo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904785.5001466,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be hot\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "due studenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904850.6903226,
            "question": "Two students.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "they are tired"
            ],
            "answer": "They are sleepy.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904811.303423,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro hanno sonno.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco otto bambini"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco otto bambini.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904835.4315345,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are eight children. (boys)\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "paura",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904813.687644,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fear\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nonna",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904838.5790393,
            "question": "Given the definition \"grandmother\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "una"
            ],
            "answer": "la",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904847.7473798,
            "question": "(a or the) Lei e' ___ madre.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "we have",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904842.6508467,
            "question": "Given the definition \"noi abbiamo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tu hai due sorelle e cinque fratelli",
                "Tu hai due sorelle e cinque fratelli"
            ],
            "answer": "Tu hai due sorelle e cinque fratelli.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904826.2076583,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You have two sisters and five brothers.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Carla ha sete"
            ],
            "answer": "Carla ha sete.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904908.8499582,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Carla is thirsty.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Y'all are in a hurry",
                "y'all are in a hurry"
            ],
            "answer": "Y'all are in a hurry.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904905.3699987,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Voi avete fretta.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ecco dodici persone"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco dodici persone.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904866.1190786,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are twelve people.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un bambino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904855.6026337,
            "question": "A boy child.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are three sisters and four brothers"
            ],
            "answer": "There are three sisters and four brothers.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904878.8868814,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono tre sorelle e quattro fratelli.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to be tired"
            ],
            "answer": "to be sleepy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904860.4743726,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere sonno\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are two students"
            ],
            "answer": "There are two students.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904883.3024008,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono due studenti.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "uno studente",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904897.1062331,
            "question": "A student.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to have",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904918.2538664,
            "question": "Given the definition \"avere\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "zio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904910.9211383,
            "question": "Given the definition \"uncle\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "You have two sisters and five brothers",
                "you have two sisters and five brothers"
            ],
            "answer": "You have two sisters and five brothers.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904932.5497835,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu hai due sorelle e cinque fratelli.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grandfather",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904939.3768196,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nonno\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fretta",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904934.6251786,
            "question": "Given the definition \"hurry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "non ho paura"
            ],
            "answer": "Io non ho paura.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904916.1090243,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am not afraid.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a nephew",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904921.6138995,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un nipote\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "caldo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904924.1174796,
            "question": "Given the definition \"heat\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Ci sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904944.101254,
            "question": "(C'e' | Ci sono) ___ il fratello e la sorella.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nonno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904977.4652858,
            "question": "Given the definition \"grandfather\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "thirsty"
            ],
            "answer": "thirst",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904951.5094795,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sete\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quattro donne",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904986.9122539,
            "question": "four women",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "uncle",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904983.000594,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"zio\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "I have",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904980.408921,
            "question": "Given the definition \"io ho\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you",
                "you (formal)O"
            ],
            "answer": "you (formal)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516904989.640844,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Lei\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be afraid",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904961.957393,
            "question": "Given the definition \"avere paura\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516904993.0892553,
            "question": "(C'e' | Ci sono) ___ il padre.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "due padri",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905042.1514235,
            "question": "two fathers",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905038.7519662,
            "question": "(C'e' | Ci sono) ___ la famiglia.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hunger",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905009.2566605,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fame\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "here are 9 girl children",
                "Here are nine girls"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are nine children. (girls)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905020.8127422,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco nove bambine.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "here are three families"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are three families.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905035.1324792,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco tre famiglie.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "here are eight baby boys",
                "Here are eight baby boys"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are eight children. (boys)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905031.1643267,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco otto bambini.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "We are cold",
                "we are cold"
            ],
            "answer": "We are cold.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905047.4563897,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi abbiamo freddo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you are thirsty",
                "You are thirsty"
            ],
            "answer": "You (informal) are thirsty.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905053.9596252,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu hai sete.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lui",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905063.2599819,
            "question": "Given the definition \"he\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be hungry",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905061.404062,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere fame\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "noi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905064.9321468,
            "question": "Given the definition \"we\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "he is",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905056.920105,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lui e'\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lei",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905076.6198645,
            "question": "Given the definition \"she\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "We are not afraid",
                "we are not afraid"
            ],
            "answer": "We are not afraid.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905074.7956347,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi non abbiamo paura.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tu",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905066.4272954,
            "question": "Given the definition \"you (informal)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am hungry"
            ],
            "answer": "I am hungry.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905086.7394793,
            "question": "Given the definition \"IO ho fame.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "He is sleepy",
                "he is tired"
            ],
            "answer": "He is sleepy.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905083.6319382,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui ha sonno.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am afraid",
                "I am afriad"
            ],
            "answer": "I am afraid.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905100.8546095,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io ho paura.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905093.7990298,
            "question": "(a or the) Io ho ___ fratello.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "io ho paura",
                "ho paura"
            ],
            "answer": "Io ho paura.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905115.311012,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am afraid.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you are afraid",
                "you are scared"
            ],
            "answer": "You (informal) are afraid.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516905125.0755427,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu hai paura.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere fretta",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905121.2115462,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be in a hurry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Carla is thirsty"
            ],
            "answer": "Carla is thirsty.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905089.9360957,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Carla ha sete.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "female cousin",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905164.3188639,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"cugina\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I have a small family"
            ],
            "answer": "I have a small family.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905144.4235506,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"io ho una famiglia piccola.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "due sorelle",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905140.0828876,
            "question": "two sisters",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ecco dieci uomini e undici donne",
                "Ecco dieci uomini e undici donne"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco dieci uomini e undici donne.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905137.110912,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are ten men and eleven women.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "male cousin",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905167.6306295,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"cugino\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "uno studente",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905158.7907777,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a (male) student\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "here are 10 men and 11 women",
                "Here are ten men and 11 women"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are ten men and eleven women.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905155.566003,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco dieci uomini e undici donne.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tre fratelli",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905171.6028085,
            "question": "three brothers",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905176.6195433,
            "question": "(a or the) Io ho ___ nonno.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "una",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905225.1541975,
            "question": "(a or the) Lei ha ___ sorella.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a niece",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905194.0188754,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"una nipote\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Ci sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905186.3225968,
            "question": "(C'e' | Ci sono) ___ la madre e il padre.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cinque poliziotti",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516905233.6063337,
            "question": "five policeman",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cugina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905211.5822122,
            "question": "Given the definition \"female cousin\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "freddo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905188.8429635,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cold\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "y'all are in a hurry"
            ],
            "answer": "Y'all are in a hurry.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905183.2185607,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Voi avete fretta.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "they",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905238.9015613,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"loro\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be hot",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905237.1012106,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere caldo\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you"
            ],
            "answer": "you (informal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905249.7495525,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"tu\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "y'all",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905252.5653772,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"voi\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "she",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905247.9261985,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lei\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere sete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905242.173691,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be thirsty\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "she has",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516905245.4292586,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lei ha\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        }
    ]
}